ptvsports.pk 2012-11-26

# Privacy Policy PTV Sports.pk

PTVSports.pk has established its own privacy policy which shows the details of personal information that how can we collect and use it. This privacy policy provides assistance in using our personal information. You can take help of this privacy policy first then you will know about your privacy policy in general. 

**Routine Information Collection**

All web servers collects information regarding their visitors including browser detail, referring pages, IP addresses, timestamps and various others. Such kinds of information are tracked for maintenance and routine. 

**Cookies and Script**

PTVSports.pk uses various means to save information regarding the preferences and history of visitor. They may use cookies to save the information for better services of the visitor with brief contents. The cookies and script may also be used by third parties including advertising partners. The use of the cookies and scripts is also meant for showing advertisement and various other information to track down to the third parties through their servers. 

**Controlling Your Privacy**

You should control your privacy by disabling the cookies from one site to the other. You can change the settings of your browser when you feel danger for your privacy. For the blocking of cookies you should seek advice from your browser documentation. In this way you can also block the tacking mechanism which disturbs your privacy. 

**Special Note About Google Advertising**

You may control all advertisements by using the cookies especially all Google based ads. The ads served by Google are allowed by the cookies to display these ads. You should have knowledge that how you can use all these cookies. If Google tracks down to intact its privacy policy through cookies or any other mechanism then it is its right to save its privacy policy. 

**Contact Information**

If any user has some queries or privacy concerns regarding this policy then he should contact with the PTVSports.pk on their website to clear it.
